我的兒
Okay son...
我知道你想讓它結束。
I know you want it to end.
我就在這裏。
I'm right here.
我就在這裏...
I'll be right here...
但不要放棄。
But do not give up.
你聽到我的話了嗎？
Do you hear me?
雖然你仍然可以屏住呼吸，但他仍在戰鬥。
While you can still hold one breath, still he is fighting.
呼吸…保持呼吸。
Breathe... keep breathing.
霍克。
Hawk.
卡爾馬。
Calma.
tmd！
Oh fuck!
該死的混蛋。
Damn bastards.
只有我們收到了關於他的。
Only we received shit about him.
你看見庫爾特了嗎？ 不
- Have you seen Coulter? - No.
嗨，這些肉什麼時候能弄乾淨？
Listen, when meat is clean...
我要你收拾好。
I want you to pack up tight.
請記住，我們包裹裏獸皮不是15張…
Remember, we do not get 15 skins on the package...
每個包裹放30張。 菲茨傑拉德。
- Do 30 skins per package. - Fitzgerald.
船長。我們怎樣來進行？
- Captain. - How are we to carry?
你覺得呢？
What do you think?
額...
Well...
無論他們在哪裏，無論他們在那裏打獵…
Think wherever they are, whether they hunt there...
我不需要另一個獵人。
I will not need another shot.
我們要趕在黎明前。
Move us ensure dawn.
今天上午已經準備好了，
Would have been ready for this morning,
我已經準備好了，如果可以的話…
I'd gone already here if my...
你知道我們現在的處境非常的不安全。
You know that we are not in safe territory.
我想這將是一個難熬的一天。
I think it will be just a few days ahead to Strong.
他們肯定會緊張…
All they have to worry...
這是給孩子們準備新鮮的肉。如果,
- It is to give the children fresh meat. - If.
如果…你見到了庫爾特嗎？
If... Have you seen Coulter?
嘿，我們放倒了頭駝鹿。
Hey we lay down a moose.
超大的一頭。
a big one.
我需要你們去幫我們。
I need help to get him.
讓我猜猜什麼時候你們剝完了皮
Let me know when to remove the skin.
我到很樂意去幫忙拿過來
I'll be happy to help then.
不，別這樣...我需要你的幫助
No, come on... friends need your help.
我們需要休息一下…
We need to rest our butts packing...
弄了這麼多的肉…
Took so long eating this damn meat...
我都開始擔心我的妻子怎麼處理這些了。
As I begin to wonder like cooking my wife.
該死，我開始想你的妻子。
Hell, I begin to wonder your wife.
閉上你的臭嘴
Shut the hell.
救命-庫爾特…
- Help. - Coulter...
該死的.是庫爾特嗎？
- Fuck. - Is that Coulter?
呆在一起.吉姆，你去找船長。
- Stay together. - Jim, look for the Captain.
基督（祈禱上帝保佑）！
Jesus Christ!
-閉嘴！快來幫我！
- Shut up! - Help me!
安靜…-沉默的聲音…
- All tuned... - Hagan silence...
該死
Damn.
那是什麼？
What was that?
我們走
Let's go.
他們在那裏。
They are upon us.
我看不到他們
I can not see them.
-趴下，TMD
- Down. - Fuck.
他們到處都是。
they're Everywhere.
我們被包圍了
We are surrounded.
-他們到處都是…
- They are everywhere. - Soho...
呆在這兒
Stay here.
不,不,奧,我的天！
No, no, no. Oh no!
待在下面
Stay below.
沒有人能離開這…
Nobody leaves outdoors...
有人爬上了這座山！
What someone climb the hill!
沒有人動，留在這兒。
Nobody move, stay where you are.
他們想要獸皮
They want skins.
如果不是你現在急著收包…
If you do not collect the packages now...
我們現在什麼都沒有了
We will lose them all.
去上船。兒子，船。
Go to the boat. The boat, son.
走,走,走.
Move, move, move.
走出這林子，走…
Get out of the forest, leaving the forest...
去船那邊
Toward the boat.
霍克！
Hawk!
霍克,霍克.
Hawk, Hawk.
拿住那些獸皮.
Grab skins.
來，拿住獸皮。
Come on, grab the skin.
拿好獸皮.
Grab skins.
安.過來。
Agrrenlas. Come on.
過來
Come on.
堅持住，我們會得到幫助…
Hold on, we'll get help...
加油，繼續走…
Come on, keep moving...
格拉斯
Glass !
快上船
Go into the boat!
該死的孫子
fuck  son ..
起來，去船那邊.
Get up, toward the boat.
救命
Help.
走，跟上.
Move, come on.
快來
Come on.
-注意-切斷繩子.
- Care. - Cut the rope.
把繩索切掉.
Cut the rope.
我要去下游.
I going downstream.
快上船.
Get in the boat.
求你們，別走，等等我.
Do not go, please.
我的女兒,頗瓦恰，他不在這兒.（這裏伏筆--待會劇情之找女兒）
My daughter, Powaqa, is not here.
快拿上我們所以能帶得動的獸皮.
Gather all the skins we can load.
這些獸皮能讓我們換到法國種馬...
Will change the skins with the French horse...
快繼續找.
And we continue searching.
塵埃還花…
And the dust returns flowers...
阿門
Amen.
當晨星在東方出現，爭鬥就結束了，我的心智就像黎明那般清淨...
When the morning was clear...
阿門
Amen.
準備好了嗎？
Ready?
別動
Do not move.
你從哪而學會的這本事？
Where did you learn that?
我的父親是一名醫生.
My father was a doctor.
-布裏傑.-船長有一小隊人馬跟著我們…
- Bridger. - Captain have a small group following us...
希望這次能完成這次交易。
Hoping to finish the job.
-按住這兒.-如果
- Hold there. - If.
告訴我你有什麼計劃。
Tell me you have some sort of plan.
格拉斯
Glass.
密蘇里的身體狀況不太好。
The Missouri is not good.
它還有口氣在。
There is still water running in it.
我們必須離開這條船…
We must get off this boat...
你想讓我們下船嗎？
Do you want to get off the boat?
我們應該怎麼辦？
What shall we do?
獸皮...
skins...
我們坐在那裏，像一群該死的狗。
And we sat there on the tail, like a bunch of damn dogs.
最穩妥的辦法是想到一個新的安排…
The safest thing to do is charting a new course...
我們走陸路
Back to earth.
對於這次「旅程」做好準備
Prepare the trip.
最好現在我們正在下沉，被那些白癡抓住。
Best sinking now, being caught those idiots.
他們現在正在盯著你呢，「乖兒子」.
Already they have eyes on you right now, son.
我想說的是我們現在被他們盯上了.
I say follow in the pot.
把船靠向岸邊…
Put the course heading to Fort...
和走水路一樣有風險。
And risk for water.
格拉斯比我們所有人都瞭解怎麼走.
Glass territory knows this better than the rest of us together.
你的任務是帶著我們安全的回去.
Your job is to bring them safely home.
-讓他待我們安全的回去？-呵呵
- Take me home safely? - If.
我必須提醒你，我們已經失去了32個人.
Do I have to remind you that we lost 32 men ?
第33個也快了.
33 already.
他們都是好樣的,菲茨傑拉德，不論多少損失。
They were my men Fitzgerald, is how many lost.
我們按照格拉斯說的做，服從命令.
We do what he says Glass, order this.
我們必須放棄水路.
We must release the boat.
如果我們繼續這麼走下去，這hallaran河就是我們的盡頭。
If we track, which Hallaran the end of the river.
最好的方案是沿著斯卡拉走
The best course is scalar field...
去Fort Kahowa（地名）.
To Fort Kahowa.
-好吧.-這樣的路線安全嗎？
- Come on. - Insurance?
我一周前去過那裏。
A week before arriving there.
至少我們要一些馬匹。
At least something to change horses.
我到知道有一個地方你可以得到。
I know of no place where you can do that.
瞭解，船長.
Well, Captain.
放棄這艘船，這是個TMD決定。
Losing the boat, it is a fucking mistake.
印第安人也不愚蠢…
Besides the Red Indians are not stupid...
如果我們堅持下去，我們就可以穿過山峰。
If we keep it, we can down across the peaks.
你的行為就像你所說的,菲茨傑拉德。
You act like you know what you're talking of Fitzgerald.
你根本沒法交流
No one is talking to you.
根本不聽建議.
Do not listen anyway.
我不相信但我不得不必須忍受這該死的…
I can not believe I have to endure this shit ...
我說...
All I say...
這是一種方式...
Camp there is a way...
但我們會死在這兒.
And we can hang in there.
我們走陸路.
We walked.
好吧，你是老大聽你的.
Yeah, sure we will.
我不大相信他，因為我都不知道他是做什麼的.
Demons can not believe I do not know his work captain.
把獸皮藏在岩石中直到我們回來…
Hide packaging in the rocks when we return...
-記住.一定要在藏得地方做上記號。
- Pick. - Be sure to mark the place.
我們為這些岩石留下了一筆財富。
We left a fortune on these rocks.
這裏沒有更多的地方可以放置，我們就搬到山上。
No more room here, we move to the hills .
格拉斯.
Glass. Charts a course...
狹窄的路可能會把我們帶到小溪旁。
The narrower may bring us near the stream.
是的
Yes, sir.
那不是對的
This is not right.
都知道，當我們返回時這些獸皮還能不能在。
All know that this forest will not here when we return.
我們沒辦法一直帶著這些獸皮
There is no way we can take them all the way ...
返回到城堡。
Back to the Fort.
我們必須這麼做…雖然存在很大的風險…
Not the way we go, well... It's a big risk...
我們將在它的領土上，希望你的雙手自由。
We will be in its territory 'll want your hands free.
我試著告訴他不要丟掉這些皮。
I try to tell him not lose these skins.
你想要和這些獸皮待在一起還是活著？
You want to stay with skins or your life?
生活？
Life?
這是什麼生活？我都快沒命了.
What life is this? I have no life.
我擁有的僅僅是自由和獲得這些獸皮而已.
I have just as freedom and get is with these skins.
TMD
Fuck!
不管如何,我都得回去...
No way, I'm going home...
我們一直忙了快六個月了，我累的就像頭騾子
I've been six months breaking my back as mule
伸著自己的脖子...
Risking my neck...
死了的話
Men dying and why?
即等於失去了一切。
Almost lost everything.
這份活計從一開始就很操蛋.
The work was fucked from the start.
我們都會沒事的.
We are well screwed.
你們想離開這裏…
And you guys want to leave it here...
因為格拉斯先生在這兒
Because Mr Glass here
能解決掉這麻煩
Is supposed to fix the damn things.
-因為他知道很多山路.-遠遠超過我們所知道的.
- Because he knows a lot of hills. - Much more than we know.
是吧？
Yes?
帶著他的兒子…
Brought his son...
我說他看起來像個野人
And it looks like a wild, if you ask me.
讓他的兒子一個人.
Leaves his son alone.
我就說說.
I'm just saying.
野人…他們是野蠻人…
Wild... They are savages...
嗨，格拉斯
Hey Glass.
他們說的是真的嗎？射中了一位中尉…
Is it true what they say? That shot a Lieutenant...
然後他生活在野蠻人中嗎？
While living among savages?
菲茨傑拉德。
Fitzgerald.
死光了士兵和21人在印第安人…
Soldiers dead and 21 others in Indian...
但你和你的兒子是唯一活著的人。
But you and your son were the only ones walk out alive.
這就像是一個奇跡，不是嗎？
It's like a miracle, is not it?
閉嘴,菲茨傑拉德。
Shut Fitzgerald.
是那樣的嗎？
Is that you?
射擊你的同伴去救這只像狗一樣的兒子？
Shoot one of your own to save this dog here?
-閉嘴。你想打孩子嗎？
- Shut up. - You want to fight child?
你和那個男孩的媽媽**嗎？
You were playing with the boy's mother?
-菲茨傑拉德！-他殺死了她？
- Fitzgerald! - He killed her?
你可以不在擦這槍了嗎？我正在跟你說話呢
You can end the rifle, I'm talking about.
我正在工作。
I'm working on it.
當我在跟你說話的時候，你就這樣做了。
You do it when you finish after talking to you.
-看著人渣.-這已經足夠！
- Look slag. - It's enough!
忘了你的孩子。
You forget your kid place.
據我所處的地方，這是一支槍。
As far as my place is here, this side rifle.
走開,菲茨傑拉德.
Move Fitzgerald.
聽我說
Listen to me.
現在只有幾個小時的時間留給我們.
We only have a few hours left us light.
我們必須藏好這些獸皮...
We must keep these skins...
並且擺脫船，快點.
And get rid of the boat, come on.
是的,船長.
Yes, Captain.
我說過你是看不出來的，孩子。
I told you were invisible, son.
-至少…如果你還想活著…
- At least... - If you want to keep closed survive...
河口【地名】
Mouth.
-至少他聽到了我…他們沒有聽到你的聲音！
- At least he heard me... - They do not hear your voice!
只看你皮膚的顏色。
Only see the color of your skin.
你明白嗎？
Do you understand?
你懂了嗎？-是的
- Do you understand? - Yes
你必須聽我的，兒子.
You must listen to me, son.
你不得不聽.
You have to listen.
貝克特.
Beckett.
韋斯頓。
Weston.
為什麼不跳呢？
Why not jump?
看起來我們似乎擺脫了他們。
It seems that changed their minds.
「聰明」的混蛋。
Clever bastards.
不錯…
Astute ...
確實該捨棄那條船。
Should be on that boat.
你是對的
You did right.
是時候出發了
It's time to move.
該起了.
Rise.
我們得走了.
Let's go.
我馬上來.
I'm coming.
你先躺著吧.
Best lie down.
當其他人準備好，我來叫你。
When other men are ready, send them to me.
我去西方.
I go to the West.
你是我的兒子
You're my son.
這兒只有兩個.
There are only two here.
頗瓦恰不在這兒
Powaqa is not here
可能別人帶走了她.
The others probably took her.
他們去了北邊.
They went north.
我們將翻越這些山。
We'll take the trail in the mountains.
這是正確的決定嗎？
Was it the right decision...?
丟下船走陸路?
Leave the boat?
我們不能繼續沿著這條河。
We could not continue down the river.
字幕
We had flanked.
如果我們繼續在地面上，山…
If we continue east on ground, mountains...
我們將節省一周的時間返回到家。
We saved a week to the Fort.
如果我們不改變任何路線的話。
That if we do not change anything on the way.
-你覺得呢
- Do you think you? - If.
菲茨傑拉德說的是真的嗎？
Is it true what Fitzgerald said?
你來這兒是為了逃避法律的制裁？
What you came here running from the law?
格拉斯,保持冷靜
Glass, just keep quiet.
你的兒子，看到了很多…
Your boy, has seen much...
你覺得有像母親的權利嗎？
Do you have a mother reunite the Right Thing?
他在這兒
There's something here.
格拉斯
Glass !
他在這兒
We have something here.
我的上帝
Christ almighty.
嗨,你
Hey, you.
嗨
Hey!
他在下面
It is below.
-快來幫我...-睜大你的眼睛
- Help me... - Keep your eyes open.
快來,我需要幫助.
Come on, I need help now.
格拉斯
Glass.
我的上帝
Oh my God!
-奧，基督-船長
- Oh Christ! - Captain.
給我破布!
Rags need now!
給我布堵住傷口
Press with rags where blood flows.
這兒
Prepare things.
布裏傑，吸起來。
Bridger, suck it up.
-安靜-我的天！
- Quiet. - God!
你不得不信他殺了那頭灰熊。
You have to give him credit for that Grizzly carried with him.
應該是射死的，整個地方都充滿了樹…
Should shoot, the whole place is full of trees damn...
那足夠了！
That's enough!
我們還在他們的領土上…
Continue in their territories...
他是一個像惡魔一樣的男人。
It is one of our men, demons.
你們去四周警戒.
Aposten a circle around us.
你們兩個去西邊和北面。
North and west, leading to the two you.
比爾，弗裏曼你們去南面和南面。
Bill, Fryman you take the South and East.
我不想聽到任何人的槍聲。
I do not want anyone to hear a shot.
-是的.-先生-我們開始縫合.
- Yes sir. - We sutured.
那我呢？
What about me?
抱歉
Sorry.
你不得不呆在這兒.
You have to stay here.
抱歉，格拉斯，我很抱歉
Sorry Mr. Glass. I am so sorry.
布裏傑，抬他起來.擠在這裏。
Bridger, suck it up. Squeeze here.
在這裏太。
Bleeds down here too.
可憐的混蛋。
Poor bastard.
做正確的事是…快完成它。
The right thing to do would be... Finish it fast.
至少這次他是成功的。
At least it has a chance of success.
看到了嗎？你看到他對灰熊做了什麼。
Be achieved? You saw what he did the Grizzly.
你將會在一個小時死去。
You are dead in an hour.
如果我們不停下來的話，我們都會。
We all will if we stop not worry about that.
相反,我認為,向前。
Colcasela instead. I argue. Ahead.
我同意，你做的
I argue, you do it.
好吧
Go! Now!
-他暈倒了。?非常好。
- he fainted. - Very good.
我會縫合，讓我看看。
I'll suture, let me see.
奧 我的天
Oh God!
水
Water.
瑞查得，告訴其他人今晚得待在這裏宿營。
Richard, tell the others camp here tonight.
-我就在這裏。是的，先生。
- I'm right here. - Yes sir.
我就在這裏…
I'll be right here...
杜桑，他們來了。
Toussaint, is here.
雖然我不該在這兒
Thought I would not make it.
我很高興你的到來
I'm glad you're here.
我需要馬和步槍.
We need horses and rifles.
我們帶來了一些獸皮.
We bring many skins.
沒有馬了...
No horses... Just what we agreed.
帶來了他們所有的獸皮.
Take all skin they want.
我們需要馬和步槍.
We need horses and rifles.
哈哈，我還需要**女人呢
And I need a woman with big tits.
你可以去做飯了。
You can cook.
我們不可能給你任何的馬了
We can not give any horse.
你說什麼？
What are you saying?
我不瞭解任何關於馬的事情
I do not know anything about horses.
拿些喝的來
Bring something to drink...
一些威士忌。
Some whiskey.
告訴他別再問關於馬的事情了.
Tell him to stop asking about the horses.
和你做生意很愉快。
Is always good to do business with you.
馬
Horses.
沒有馬
Horses no.
我們可以交換武器和彈藥。
All we can exchange weapons and ammunition is .
告訴他，如果他再問馬，就不在交易了。
Tell him if he asks again for horses, no deal.
這是哪裏？
Where did this?
美國人又怎麼了？
How Americans?
已經標注。
Are already marked.
我只能半價出售給他們。
I can only sell them at half price.
他離開這裏。
Him out of here.
我說了沒有馬了
I said no horses.
我們帶著這三匹馬。
We take these three horses.
我不會再說第二遍
I will not say it again.
他們不是交易的一部分。
They are not part of the deal.
現在告訴你的人離開。
Now tell your man to stay away.
我們有一個協議，你必須履行它。
We had an agreement, you have to honor it.
你站在這兒跟我談協議？
You stand there to speak of honor?
我告訴你說法語。
I told you speak French.
所有這些皮都是偷來的。
All of these skins are stolen.
不
No.
你已經偷來了所有的一切。
You have stolen everything to us.
所有
All!
土地
Earth.
動物
Animals.
兩個白人男子進入…
Two white men got into...
我的村莊，帶著我的女兒，頗瓦恰。
My village and took my daughter, Powaqa.
我們離開這些皮是因為榮譽需要它。
We leave these skins because honor demands it.
我將會騎著你的馬去找我的女兒。
I will take your horses to find my daughter.
你不可能試圖去阻止我。
You are free to try and stop me.
According .
生意是生意。
Business is business.
準備五匹馬給他們。
Prepare five horses for them.
字幕
I want everyone to be raised and ready to dawn.
是的，先生.
Yes, sir. I got this.
帶著格拉斯負走將會是很困難。
Glass Load to be difficult.
我們必須盡可能地向前走。
We must move forward as far as possible.
我們將分為2組。
We will divide into two groups.
瓊斯，菲茨傑拉德，和我。我們走在河的東邊。
Fitzgerald, Jones, me. We take the east side of the river.
安德森探索前進。
Anderson explore ahead.
其他人繼續帶著格拉斯
- Are only claws. - The remaining charge to Glass.
是的,船長
Yes, Captain.
他們不是我。
They are not for me.
別讓他掉到水裏…
Do not let him fall into the water...
跟上
Come on.
-後退。夠了！
- Back. - It's enough!
該死，別讓它掉下來！
Damn, do not let it fall!
別讓它掉下來！
Do not let him fall.
小心點
Care.
我們怎麼上去？
How are we going to achieve this?
只是多一點。
Just a little more.
我們沒力氣了船長
We will not Captain power.
跟著布拉傑
Follow up Bridger.
繼續走
Keep going...
I gain...
現在...
Now, now...
抓住
Hold it.
這該死的。我們做不到。
Enough of this shit. We not make it so.
船長，他在發燒。
Captain's burning.
船長，沒有意義的…
Captain no sense...
做一個有利於他離開痛苦的決定吧。
Does not do a favor to leave a suffering as well.
船長
Captain!
船長，上面什麼都沒有，我們得回去了。
Captain, is everything as above. We have to go back.
找另一條路。
Find another way.
過來
Suck it up.
嗨 格拉斯
Hugh Glass ......
抱歉
Sorry.
布拉傑，那塊布把他的眼鏡蒙上吧
Put a cloth over her eyes Mr. Bridger.
什麼？不，先生，別這樣
- What? - Sir, I can not.
放塊布蒙上他的眼鏡
Put a cloth over his eyes.
-等等，-抱歉
- Wait. - Sorry Hugh.
-等等。沒有他我們怎麼回去？先生，我不能。
- Wait. How to return without him? - Sir, I can not.
-它是唯一一個認識路的。-你不能這麼做。
- It is the only one who knows the way. - You can not keep more.
把布放在他的眼睛上。
Put a cloth over his eyes.
主啊，我不能。
Lord, I can not.
等等，你不能
Wait, you can not...
把布放在他的眼睛上。
Put a cloth over his eyes.
字幕
Back up.
停止，亨利先生…
Stop, Mr. Henry...
亨利，求你了。
Henry, please.
船長，船長...
Captain, Captain...
嗨，閉嘴！
Hey, shut up!
冷靜孩子
Calm down boy.
冷靜
Calm down.
亨利，求你了...
Henry, please...
在落基斯公司有70美元…
There are $ 70 bonus in Rockies the company...
留下兩個人，誰留下..
Two men, who remain...
帶著格拉斯回去
Back to Glass, until it's over.
-我留下.-我也是
- I'll stay. - I also.
不管有沒有錢我都留下。
With or without money, I stay.
我還需要一個人
I need a third party.
抱歉船長，我還有家人...
Sorry Captain, I have family...
我還沒那麼瘋狂
I'm not crazy.
船長，三個人不可能完成的
Captain, three men can not hold a party Reds.
何況還有男孩
Much less about boys.
另外，70美元不會讓人信服的.
In addition, $ 70 will not convince anyone.
那100美元呢
100 then.
這個男的是我們活著的唯一理由
This man is the only reason why we're still alive.
TMD，船長，開始的時候我們有45個人，現在只有10個，待會可能只剩下9個了
Fuck Captain, were 45 men when we started, now 10, almost 9
你是我的父親願意和你分享
You Are my father can have my share.
我也是
Mine too.
我的一部分。
My part as well.
好吧
Okay.
很好，如果布拉傑先生覺得，那我就呆在這兒.
Well, if Mr. Bridger feels the same way, I'll stay.
-你？-如果
- You? - If.
我已經丟掉了我的獸皮的收益...
I've lost my share of skins...
所以我不得不找一些額外的收入
So I have no choice but to look for other income .
所以多呆在這兒一兩天也不會有什麼不同
Also be here a day or two most not make a difference.
200美元，帶著他回家
$ 200, is bringing something go home.
你需要照顧好格拉斯直到結束.
You need to take care Glass until the time comes.
明白了嗎？
Understand?
是的，先生，你知道我的
Si. Yes, you have my word.
先生們，趕在天黑之前把他放在安全的地方吧
Guys, Lower him to some safer place before nightfall.
字幕
Already they have heard guys.
-菲茨傑拉德。隊長。
- Fitzgerald. - Captain.
你必須照顧好格拉斯.
Glass must be careful much time as needed.
當死神來臨的時候，給他一個適當的埋葬。
Y a proper burial when the time comes. He earned.
我懂得
Understood.
父親，你能聽到風嗎？
Can you hear the wind, Father?
你還記得我媽媽過去常常說的什麼嗎？
Do you remember what my mother used to say wind?
風不可能吹倒一棵有根的樹。
Wind can not beat a tree with strong roots.
保持呼吸...
Still breathe...
我非常的想念她
I miss her so much.
我就在這裏…
I'll be right here...
I'm right here.
雖然你仍然可以屏住呼吸，但他仍在戰鬥。
While you can still hold one breath, still he is fighting.
吸氣，保持呼吸.
Breathe. Keep breathing.
當暴風雪來臨的時候…
When a storm...
你正站在一棵樹的前面…
And you're standing in front of a tree...
如果你看見樹枝要墜落…
If you see the branches swear to be falling...
但是如果你看到了樹幹，你會注意到它很穩定。
But if you see the trunk, you notice stability.
300美元是不可忽視的…
$ 300 is something not negligible...
我會去德克薩斯，我買一塊像樣的土地…
I will go to Texas, I buy a decent piece of land ...
我去如廁。
And I will begin to urinate into the wild.
我離開這個鬼地方。
I leave this godforsaken place.
你這樣做嗎？
The Reds you do that?
只是想知道。
Just wondering.
他們做了。
They did.
他們生活好了之後就搬進了城市
They took the city in which he was well.
一開始我就一無所有，
At the beginning I felt nothing,
只聽到聲音…
Only hear the sound...
刀刮我的頭骨，你知道…
Knife scraping my skull, you know...
他們笑著，喊著，砰的一聲…
They laughed and shouted and banged...
然後是血…
Then came the blood ...
寒冷開始侵襲我的臉和我的眼睛…
Cold started running down my face and my eyes...
呼吸…
The breathing...
我差點被淹死了。
I was drowning in it.
那是當我感覺到它。
That's when I felt it.
感覺到任何事
I felt everything.
我把我的頭向後靠。
Toned I had my head backwards.
耶穌
Jesus.
是的，所以我要去德克薩斯…
Yes, so I'm going to Texas...
搶你，卻不拿你的頭。
Rob you, but do not take your head.
它是怎樣的？
How was it?
你能停止噪音嗎？
Could you please stop that noise?
我想說的是...丟掉它
I just... Leave it.
那些不能幫助你的人。
I'm full of skin and with guys who can not help you.
我們爬上了山，所以他們就不會再繼續追了。
We climb the mountains damn so that we do not continue chasing.
如果你準備好了…
If you are ready...
享受這聖餐。
Take the sacrament.
我可以為你做。
I can do for you.
格拉斯你知道什麼
What you cling Glass?
你想知道？
You know?
這將變得更好...
It would be better...
如果你給了那最後的呼吸。
If you gave that last breath now.
為了我們
For all of us.
一些事
That's something.
我懇求你格拉斯，
I beg Glass,
印第安人離我們很近，我甚至可以問到他們...
Reds are so close I can smell them now...
並且我知道你也可以，所以你不得不去考慮
And I know that you can smell them, and you have to think.
為你自己，和你的孩子.
Think of your boy.
很好，因為你將要殺了他。
Good, because you're going to kill him.
我們將殺了他們.
We will kill them all.
如果你想要的話我可以幫助你。
I can help if you want.
釋放痛苦非常快速和容易的…
Quitarte suffering very fast and easy...
我想誰也不知道是你放棄了他。
Nobody has to know that you gave up. I would.
你所要做的只是眨一下眼鏡…
All you have to do is blink...
如果你想讓我這樣做的話。
If you want me to do that.
救你的兒子和眨一下眼睛
Save your guy and flashes.
可以的話你就眨下眼。
Just blink.
好的
yeahi.
奧，好的
Oh, yes!
願上帝保佑你.
Hopefully the good Lord, us out of here soon.
也許原諒你的罪過，你知道，也許不是…
May forgive your sins, you know, maybe not...
你必須向主投降。
You must surrender to the Lord.
在基督裏，主憐憫…
In Jesus Christ, the Lord have mercy...
別動，滾開。
Stay away. Get away.
你還好嗎？吉姆。吉姆…幫助。
Are you okay? Jim. Jim... Help.
-幫助。平靜。好了，不要喊。
- Help. - Calm. Well, do not shout.
-不要尖叫，你這樣會殺死我們。讓我們走。
- Do not scream, you want to kill us. - Let go.
我會告訴你你做了什麼，你會死的.
I'll tell you what you did and you will hang.
-你必須明白…
- You have to understand that... - You hang, quotes...
Help. 吉姆快來。
Help. Jim come here.
睡吧孩子…
Silence guy...
TMD
Fuck.
你得生點火來做食餵他
You have to feed the fire.
他的呼吸變了。
His breathing changed.
注意。
Noticed.
我的天，他冷得像冰一樣。
Hell, is cold as ice.
這兒，格拉斯先生...抬起頭
Here Mr. Glass... This head...
這將使你感到溫暖
Will keep you warm.
好的
Okay.
霍克在哪裏？
Where is Hawk?
他不是和你在一起嗎？
Was not he with you?
沒有.-沒有？
- No. - No?
我懂，格拉斯先生
I understand Mr. Glass.
很好
Good.
我想我會去看看我是否能找到。
I think I'll go see if I can find .
是的，這聽起來是個好主意。
Yes, it sounds like a good idea.
霍克
Hawk!
…你殺了我的兒子。
... You killed my son.
霍克
Hawk!
布拉傑，有大約20個人沿著河流走
Bridge, there are about 20 Reds for the stream.
到這兒來。
Come over here.
收拾你的東西，讓我們走。
Pick up your shit and let's go.
TMD,等等，我們該怎麼做？
Fuck. Wait. What do we do?
快跑，馬上.
Running, now.
-霍克怎麼辦？-這已不再是我們的問題。
- And what about Hawk? - It is no longer our problem.
我們不能離開這裏。
We can not leave here.
他應該是在找我們
He is supposed browser.
他會找到它嗎？
Will she find it?
等等，格拉斯怎麼辦？
Wait. What about Glass?
我們現在有更大的麻煩，還有他的兒子
We have more problems than he, is now on his own.
不，不，我們發過誓的，要帶他離開…
No, no, we made a promise Captain...
你必須給他一個適當的葬禮當時候到來。
You have to give him a proper burial when the time comes.
你需要一支槍。
Well you need a rifle.
你不能做任何事情，你不能用你的手。
You can not do anything with one, you can not use your hands.
不，不，我們不能這樣做。
No, no, we can not do this.
-我們別無選擇。-我們不能.看。
- We have no fucking choice. - We can not. Look.
-好，葬禮…-你在幹什麼？
- Well, a funeral... - What are you doing?
你想要帶著他？來吧。
Do you want to take? Come on.
不，等等...
No, wait...
冷靜，聽著……
Calma, Fitz slowly...
冷靜
Calma.
-我不能…-該死…
- I can not... - Damn...
倒霉
Shit.
等等，等等
Wait, wait...
等等
Wait!
閉嘴
Shut up.
等等
Wait.
菲茨...
Fitz...
你在幹什麼？
what are you doing? - Like what do I do?
一個適當的埋葬。
A proper burial.
像承諾的那樣。
As promised.
-不，不。-為什麼不呢？
- No, not so. - Why not?
格拉斯仍然活著。它活著。
Glass is still alive. Its alive.
那就槍殺了他。
so shoot him.
我們不得不走了
I have to go.
抱歉
Sorry.
抱歉，抱歉
Sorry, sorry.
船長，在這裏…
Captain, over here...
這下面有一條路。
There is a path below.
沒辦法通過經過。
No way to pass down here.
船長，我們必須爬過去
Captain, we must climb.
-穿過去的時候當心點。我們可能會掉下去.
- Cross over carefully. - O may all go to hell.
-地圖上說什麼？-繼續攀登。
- What does the map say? - Keep climbing.
爬上去，船長。
Climbed Captain.
我們繼續攀登。
We continue climbing.
直到我們到家。
Until we reach Fort.
跟上
Come on.
-我們必須離開這裏-如果。是的
- We must get out of here. - yeah.
我們已經快接近了。
We are already closer.
船長
Captain.
主…讓我把他們帶回去吧。
Lord... Let me take this.
跟誰？
Who I follow?
跟隨你想要跟著的人。
Follow whoever you want.
我得到。
I gain.
布萊爾，來這兒！
Blair, come here!
我不會離開你的，我的兒.
I will not leave you, son.
我在這兒
I'm right here.
這火焰即將燃燒殆盡.
The fire is finished.
別睡了...
Should not rest...
我們必須保持印第安人和我們之間的距離。
We must also put distance between the Reds and us.
好的
Well
印第安人不可能和我們一樣快
A dozen Reds may not be as fast as us.
-20.什麼？
- 20. - What?
我想說昨天你說你看到了20個印第安人
I thought you said you saw a 20 Reds.
你在說什麼？
What are you talking about?
你把我叫醒了。
you woke me up。
你說你在小溪下看到了20個印第安人。
You said you saw 20 Reds down the stream.
20或十幾，沒有問題…
If 20 or a dozen, no matter...
不打算告訴你留下來…
Not going to tell you to stay...
他們穿過了河，對嗎？
Their cursed pens in the river, right?
菲茨傑拉德。
Fitzgerald.
當時你在河邊幹什麼？
What were you doing by the river by yourself?
那時我們已經有足夠的水了。
We already had plenty of water.
嗨
Hey!
菲茨傑拉德回答我，我在問你話呢
Fitzgerald Answer me, I asked you a question.
不要去問那些不重要的事情…
Do not go questioning by things that are not important...
回答我，否則我會打爆你的頭。
Answer me or I'll blow your fucking head.
你可以射任何人
You can shoot everybody.
你現在還是會死在水裏了
You'd still be back sunk in the water right now...
如果不是我
If it was not for me.
我不會回答這個問題
I do not answer questions...
你不需要知道你在問什麼
You do not want to know what you're asking.
你想要知道為什麼丟下格拉斯讓他去死？
You want to know why you left Glass back to die?
也許
Maybe...
如果你不是一個小男孩你就不會知道他不可能活更久了
If you were not a little boy 'd know he was no longer alive.
我撒了謊，因為你還不是一個男人。
I tell lies because you're not a man.
是嗎？因為你害怕死亡...
Yes? Because you were afraid of death...
並且現在還在害怕，放下槍
And afraid now, lowers the rifle.
-印第安人。-怎麼回事？
- The Reds. - What about it?
告訴我你說的哪句是真的
Tell me now and honest in what you say.
-放下槍.-你看到了印第安人了嗎？
- Lower your rifle now. - You saw the Reds?
不
No.
一個都沒有
Neither one.
你居然騙我？
You lied to me?
我欺騙了我
you lied me.
我不得不選擇正確的方式
I had to get into right guy.
從現在開始，不再談論什麼…
From now on, no talk more about...
別再說什麼了…懂嗎？
Do not no point in what is already done... Understand?
現在是在上帝的手中…
Is now in God's hands...
神所賜的，是神所賜的。
And what God gives, God takes.
倒霉
Shit.
起來，跟上。
Get up, come on.
下一次，如果你還想要射擊某人...
Next time, if you want to shoot someone...
最好使用你自己的
Better than you use... Better use powder...
改進你的步槍。
Improve your rifle.
快
Come on...
跟上，快。
Follow. Come on.
真血。頗瓦恰。
True Blood. Could Powaqa.
一個死掉了小男孩
A dead boy.
一個男孩波尼。
A boy Pawnee.
我們走
Let's go.
繼續向前
Go ahead.
-誰做的？我不知道。
- Who did this? - I do not know.
他們在這裏留下了一些東西。
They put some order around here.
這些印第安人從來沒有像你想像的那樣死去。
These Indians are never as dead as you think.
看看他們，總是像臭狗屎。
Look at them, always reek of shit.
這裏有馬。
We have horses here.
快
Come on.
馬
horses.
我們的抓住他們...
We catch ...
孩子你去另一邊抓他們。
Go into the side kid.
你在想你死去的兒子？
You want to die son?
你在合適的的地方。
You are in the right place.
我想。
I guess.
-如果我們不可能幫助…-不
- Can not help thinking if we... - No.
沒有地方可以問。
No place to ask.
上帝為我們指引了道路，他們沒有選擇。
The good Lord puts us in the way, they have not chosen.
我爸爸是個虔誠教徒，你知道嗎？
My dad you were a religious man, you know?
我可以做它，殺死它或吃它…
I could do grow it, kill it or eat it...
無論他做任何事我都無條件的相信
And just he made it without believing and nothing was it.
有一次他去打獵。
And once he went hunting Hills.
打獵
Hunting Hills...
他遇到了一些過去和他一起打獵的朋友.
He met some friends Texans and went hunting.
在這之前他已經有了幾百次的經驗
It was routine had done hundreds of times before.
三天的屠殺，TMD但在星期六結束了…
Were three days of slaughter, but ended Saturday fucking...
不知怎的在夜裏失去了他的朋友…
Somehow at night had lost his friends...
和所有的一切
And apart from all...
印第安人偷了他們的馬
Comanches stole them horses...
我餓了
I was hungry,
他爬進泥裏…
And he crawled in the mud...
在一組樹中間…
In a group of trees in the middle of nowhere...
我進入了那該死的「海洋」…
I got into that ocean of shit...
並且在那裏他找到了信仰。
And there he found religion.
一直
At that time...
他說...
He said...
他見到了上帝.
He found God.
它...
It...
「上帝"...
"God"...
是一隻松鼠。
Was a squirrel.
是的，他曾經見過他
Si. She met him once...
他就說我發現
了上帝I found God, he would say.
他坐在那裏聊天…
He sat and talked...
他光榮與崇高的虔誠…
His glory and sublime piety...
但是我槍殺了個混蛋…
And I shot the motherfucker...
威爾，睡覺吧
will  you close your eyes guy.
我受傷了。
I'm hurt.
你遇到了什麼事？
What happened to you?
一隻灰熊
A bear.
灰熊。
A Grizzly.
我的朋友…他們丟下了我。
My men... They left me for dead.
並殺了我的兒子
Killed my son.
我也失去了家人.
I lost my family too.
蘇人殺了我的人。
The Sioux killed my people.
我要去南方找更多的人。
I go south to find more Pawnee.
我的心在流血…
My heart bleeds...
但復仇是在造物主的手中。
But revenge is in the hands of the creator.
我帶著你一起
Will travel with me...
你的身體都快爛了。
Your body is rotten.
你需要趕快處理
You need to heal.
不然的話你可能會死掉
You could die.
是的
Yes!
這兒
There.
我們造的
We made it.
你應該為我們感到自豪孩子
You should be proud of you boy.
是
Si.
我們服從命令…只是省略了葬禮的一部分。
Follow orders... Just omit the part of the funeral.
不要再問一些關於良心的問題，好嗎？
Do not go down there with problems of conscience, right?
現在，我們得做我們應該做的
Now, we did what we had to do.
我們會拿出一天時間，所以深入挖掘…
We had an extra day, so dig a little deeper...
放在了野外的石頭上..
Put rocks over for wild...
他們將不會對屍體做任何事情。
They will do nothing to the body.
他被埋葬了。
He was well buried.
-主…真相就是如此…
- Lord... - The truth is...
當霍克消失了，他（格拉斯）擔心他被野人抓走了。
When Hawk disappeared he was worried about the savages.
…我馬上就要準備去找霍克。
... I was ready to leave immediately.
布拉傑這裏，要求我留下來。
Bridger here, asked to stay.
要我和他待在一起知道他死去
Asked to stay until his death...
他至少修建了十字架…
Him at least built the cross with something...
並且他把格拉斯放在了墳墓裏，給了他想要的東西…
And he puts over the grave Glass, and gave him what he wanted...
-這是我們所做的。布裏傑先生在那呆了會。
- It is what we did. - Happy that Mr. Bridger stay.
就會知道他會的。
Would know he would.
更重要的是，這個人就是我的夥伴。
More importantly Captain, this man here is my partner.
很好
Good.
我必須假設我們的治療沒有改變嗎？
Do I have to assume that our treatment has not changed?
我的運氣不錯。
To my fortune not.
謝謝你們
Thanks.
用你們的勇氣，榮譽
By their courage, honor...
-和生存
- And services. - If.
布拉傑不管你做的還是沒有做的，都值得了。
Deal or no deal with Mr Bridger, deserves for what he did.
謝謝
Thanks.
這孩子一直都這樣.
The boy has torn all the way.
他也看到了格拉斯，所以不會作假，對嗎？
All saw the way he was Glass, you could not make it, right?
是的
Si.
我們都看到了
All we saw.
為什麼你不準備呢？
Why do not you prepare?
下次
Next.
一次。
Out at a time.
當暴風雪來的時候...
When a storm...
你正站在一棵樹的前面…
And you're standing in front of a tree...
如果你看見樹枝要墜落…
If you see the branches swear to be falling...
但是如果你看到了樹幹，你會注意到它很穩定。
But if you see the trunk, you notice stability.
有一個營地的痕跡…
There are traces of a camp...
哪裏
Where?
進入月亮森林的。
Entering the forest moon.
也許離開了兩天,他們向東移動了。
Perhaps two days away. They move to the East.
去告訴其他人
Tell the others.
快去. 頗瓦恰可能和他們在一起！
Move fast. Powaqa can be with them!
把那女孩帶來…
Bring the girl...
那五匹馬不太安靜。
Those five horses were not to free.
別出聲。
Do not make a sound.
安靜
Silence.
我要一匹馬。
I will seek a horse.
我會把你蛋蛋割掉。
I will cut your balls.
杜桑去哪裏了？
Where is Toussaint?
過來...
Come...
我可以加入他們嗎？如果。
- Can I join them? - If.
-是的
- Yes? - If.
我擔心他什麼時候可以支付每筆
I wondered when it would pay per carry.
我們收集的獸皮仍然在外面…
We collect skins are still out there...
都是髒兮兮的，但那不是我的錯。
Are dirty and snow, but that's not my fault.
我希望隊長沃斯帶著他的軍隊…
I hope Captain Leavenworth arrives with his army...
和有足夠的人…
And then have the sufficient men...
在回到那裏，向那些土著展示我們強大的文明…
To back out there and show civilization...
對那些該死的印第安人，並拿回我們的獸皮。
Those damn Reds, and recover our skins.
很好,很好。
Good, good.
現在應該是什麼時候發生的？
And now when supposed to happen is that?
我不知道，但是...
I do not know, but...
不到那個時候，不會有人得到報酬得。
Until then nobody gets paid.
聽著，好嗎？
Listen, okay?
…這份工作真的太艱難了…
... It was hard to get all worked hard...
就像我看到的...的保證安全，
As I see... have a safe,
-全部的錢。-你簽了合同的。
- Full of money. - You signed a contract.
保護你的老闆的財產和你的老闆。
To protect your boss property and your boss.
現在在我的保險櫃裏，連300美元都沒有。
And in my safe is no longer full, $ 300 falls short.
這到底是什麼意思？
What the hell does that mean?
根據我的記錄現金…
According to my records cash...
由於公司的原因你錯過了它
With what you missed in issuing you end up owing the company.
新年快樂，菲茨傑拉德先生。
Happy New Year, Mr. Fitzgerald.
菲茨傑拉德殺死了我的兒子
Fitzgerald killed my son
有個白人在門外
White man at the door.
幹什麼？你是誰？
What? Who you are?
我沒有武器，我沒有武器。
I have no arms, I have no weapons.
-多布，去叫隊長。-我沒有武器。
- Dobb, looking Captain. - I have no weapon.
你有什麼事？
What about your men?
-死了，都死了。-誰？
- Dead, all dead. - Who was?
我不知道，有什麼吃的東西嗎。
I do not know, something to eat please.
那是要價的。
That is priceless.
-我沒有錢。—那就別吃了，該死的。
- I have no money. - Then do not eat it, that's that shit.
也許你可以歸還被偷得獸皮來改變了印第安人的看法。
Perhaps you can return stolen furs you changed the Indians.
約翰，西爾弗
- Now there Johns. - Silver.
奧，真的嗎？
Oh, really?
就這些麼？
Is that all you got?
9…但我的朋友都在暴風雪中死了…
Were 9... But my friend died in the snowstorm...
其他人…
And the others were...
狼…狼…被狼...
By wolves... wolves... By
等等，你從哪兒得到了它（爐石傳說的標誌，也是醉了）？
Wait where did you get this?
吃飯的地方
The canteen.
他…他摔倒在雪地裏。
He... He fell in the snow.
-誰？-我不知道，我沒有。我看不見。
- Who? - I do not know, I did not. I did not see.
可能是霍克
Could Hawk.
-是的，可能是。-還會有誰？
- Yeah, it could be. - Who else would?
-也許是西方。離這兒多遠？
- Maybe it was the West. - How far from here?
離這兒多遠？大約20公里…
- How far from here? - Some 20 kilometers...
在東北方向…靠近黃石灘。
By Northeast... Near Yellowstone.
準備好馬。
Saddle up the horses.
拿好武器，去的人每個給10美元。
Supplies and weapons, $ 10 per man.
-安德森，你留在這裏。-是的，先生。
- Anderson, you stay here. - Yes sir.
我要去喝一杯。
I'll get a drink.
把門打開
Open the door.
所有人停留調整。
All stay tuned.
睜大眼睛
Eyes front.
放慢腳步
Soft.
緩慢
Slowly.
你是誰？
Who are you?
Beckett? Are you?
韋斯頓？
Weston?
格拉斯
Glass.
-是的...是格拉斯-格拉斯...
- Is... Glass - Glass...
是的
Okay.
感謝耶穌
Jesus Christ.
感謝基督，發生了什麼事？
Jesus Christ, what happened?
他在哪兒？
Where is he?
約翰帶著他，來吧。
Johns take it, come on.
快，向前
Come on, go ahead.
-菲爾-抓住布裏傑.
- Phil. - Grab Bridger.
去找到布裏傑.
Grab Bridger.
-我找到了格拉斯.-快去
- You I have Glass. - Come on.
打開門
Open the door.
-你見過菲茨傑拉德嗎？沒有，先生。
- Have you seen Fitzgerald? - No sir.
起來
Rise.
給我起來
-你看到了菲茨傑拉德嗎？沒有，先生。
- Have you seen Fitzgerald? - No sir.
菲茨傑拉德。
Fitzgerald.
-卡爾馬。-他在哪兒？
- Calma. - Where was he?
-誰？菲茨傑拉德。
- Who? - Fitzgerald.
他去哪了？
Where did it go?
-他沒有告訴我。告訴我，否則我會打爆你的頭。
- He did not tell me. - Tell me or I'll rip your head.
-我向上帝發誓，船長。告訴我！
- I swear to God, Captain. - Tell me!
-你告訴我！-和德克薩斯。
- Tell me! - A Texas.
-德克薩斯？-他說他要去德克薩斯。
- Texas? - He said he was going to Texas.
我向上帝發誓，他說這將重新開始。
I swear to God, he said it would re-enlist.
他說想要購買一塊土地…
And he began to talk of buying, decent a piece of land...
打算去德克薩斯。我向上帝發誓。
Going to Texas. I swear to god.
呆在這兒.
Stay here.
菲茨傑拉德。
Fitzgerald.
惡魔。
Demons.
詛咒。
Curse.
打開門
Open the door.
打開它。
Open it.
找到船長
Find the Captain.
快帶著他去找醫生。
Take him to the doctor, now.
你說他死了。
You said he was dead.
-你說他死了。我以為他死了，我發誓。
- You said he was dead. - I thought he was dead, I swear.
-你是個騙子。是他逼我做的。
- You're a liar. - He forced me.
騙子，你離開。你離開了那裏。
Liar, you left. You left out there.
-抱歉...-念祈禱文
- Sorry... - Mr. Di prayer.
-什麼？-念祈禱文吧
- What? - Mr. Di prayer.
我們的身父...
Our Father...
誰在天上…我不能…
Who art in heaven... I can not...
閉嘴.
Shut up.
閉嘴！現在你是一個被指控叛國的囚犯。
Shut up! Since you are now a prisoner on charges of treason.
把他關進籠子裏。把他關進籠子裏。
Put him in a cage. Put him in a cage.
把他關起來，否則我就開槍打你！
Lock him up or I'll shoot you!
以為我會死。
Thought I would die.
-我不知道該怎麼辦…
- Arise. - I did not know what to do...
我不能幫助。
I could not help, please.
-船長..,求你-上帝！
- Captain... Please - God!
好的，來吧
Okay. Come on.
-怎麼樣了？-你會很好，沒有腫脹…
- How are you? - You'll be fine, no swelling...
你需要休息
You need rest.
我就是回來看這個。
I'll come back to see this.
他跑了，是嗎？
He escaped, right?
布裏傑說的是真的…
Bridger tells the truth...
-怎麼了？菲茨傑拉德撒謊…
- How is that? - Fitzgerald lied...
他只是在下命令。
He was only following orders.
我是不在在那裏當菲茨傑拉德刺傷殺死我的兒子。
I was not there when Fitzgerald stabbed to kill my son.
發生了什麼？他殺了霍克？
Is that what happened? He killed Hawk?
我需要一匹馬和一桿槍。
I need a horse and a gun.
不，你現在需要休息和補充體力.
No, you need to rest and something to eat.
-我要區追他-不
- I'm going after him. - No.
-你不會找到他沒有我的話。
- You will not find him without me.
-我不想讓他跑掉。
- I do not expect nor dawn and escaped.
他跑不掉的
It will not.
恐懼
Afraid.
你知道我走了多遠。
You know how far I came.
害怕，
Afraid,
我會把他帶到回來的…
I'll get him there, just...
-他還不知道。-你怎麼能這麼肯定？
- He does not know yet. - How can you be so sure?
我已經沒有什麼可以失去的了。
I have nothing to lose.
我所有的全部就是霍克…
All I had was that guy...
但他從我身上奪走了他的命。And he took it from me.
我不能讓你回去
I can not let you go back out there.
-不能再次,-不行
- Not again. - No.
我不再害怕死亡。
I have no more fear of dying.
我準備好了
I already did.
我和你一起去
I'm going with you.
有馬的痕跡。是的
Are horse trails. Yes.
沒有辦法繼續行走在夜裏。
There is no way to continue overnight.
還有多遠？
How far ahead?
?中間最大的痕跡，可能是印第安人的。
- Middle maximum day. - Could be the Reds.
如果不是他，我們就找不到了。
If not him, we lose.
現實與正義的殺戮。
Be realistic and justified kill again.
你的印痕在這裏是對的。
Your prints are right here.
快
Come on.
我都快記不得我妻子什麼樣了。
I can not remember the face of my wife.
上周我還和我在一起。
Last week I was still with me.
現在就記不住了
Now it is not.
我不擔心，當你回家的時候。
I worry not recognize, when you return home.
你殺了一個軍官，這是真的嗎？
Is it true that you killed an officer?
我殺了一個試圖殺死我兒子的人。
I just killed a man who tried to kill my son.
- 煙。-多近了？
- Smoke. - How close?
不超過一公里但是有兩條路
No more kilometer and a half that way.
我去西邊你去東面…
I go to the west and you see the East...
-我們看我們是否發現了一些痕跡。如果是印第安人呢？
- We see if we find some traces. - What if the Reds are?
如果是印第安人，你馬上回到這裏來
If you are red, you turn immediately to be here.
嗨
Hey!
不希望看到他的地位的人…
Not expecting to see a man of his status ...
到目前為止，…
Fort so far, when...
這麼冷的天，船長，你是迷路了嗎？
So cold this morning Captain, are you lost?
我是來帶你回去的。
I'm here to take you back to Fort Kahowa.
你將被帶去那裏因為謀殺而得到審判。
Where you will be taken to trial for murder.
是的，先生
Yes, sir?
這不是一個瘋狂的計劃.
I'm not crazy plan.
另外，我只發現了你一個人
In addition, I have one of your own.
格拉斯我已經做的很好了
Glass We had a deal.
我試著去告訴你的孩子。如果？
I tried to tell your kid. If?
試著告訴發生了什麼事，但他沒有聽…
Try telling what was happening, but he did not listen ...
他一直在尖叫。他將把印第安人都引過來。
And still he is screaming. He is going to appeal to everyone.
你和我...
You and I...
得解決
Had a deal.
我不知道你在外面發生了什麼
I do not know what happened out there.
但我欠主的心，
But I owe my soul to the Lord,
上帝知道發生了什麼。
Lord knows what happened out there.
不可能。
No deal.
你殺了我兒子
You killed my son.
或許你應該像個男人…
Maybe you should have raised a man...
而不是一個尖叫的小母狗。
Instead of a screaming little bitch.
該死
Damn!
你來只是為了報復。
You came all this way just for your revenge.
格拉斯你很享受這一切嗎？
Is the enjoyed Glass?
因為沒有什麼會讓你的孩子回來了。
Because nothing will return to your child.
復仇是在上帝的手中…
Revenge is in God's hands...
不是我
Not mine.